Battle.create(question_text: "Veigar is about to finish you off with his ult! Which item would protect you from the damage?" ,possible_answers: [[1,3102],[2,3101],[3,3110],[4,3135]], correct_answer: 1)
Battle.create(question_text: "The enemy team is building large amounts of armor! Which item would help you get through some of it?"  ,possible_answers: [[1,3035],[2,3102],[3,3028],[4,3022]], correct_answer: 1)
Battle.create(question_text: "The enemy team is building large amounts of magic resist! Which item would help you cut through some of it?" ,possible_answers: [[1,3135],[2,3117],[3,3123],[4,3112]], correct_answer: 1)
Battle.create(question_text: "The enemy team has many champions with crowd control spells. Which item would give you more time to control your character?" ,possible_answers: [[1,3111],[2,3078],[3,3098],[4,3100]], correct_answer: 1)
# Battle.create(question_text: "You've learned from the internet that it is a bad idea to face check bushes. Which trinket would be best for checking if anyone is hiding in a bush from far away?" ,possible_answers: [[1,3363],[2,3262],[3,3361],[4,3364]], correct_answer: 1)
Battle.create(question_text: "Which pair of boots would allow you to cast your summoner spells more often?" ,possible_answers: [[1,3158],[2,3006],[3,3009],[4,3047]], correct_answer: 1)

Battle.create(question_text: "Which support item would allow you to shield your allies based on your own health?" ,possible_answers: [[1,3401],[2,3092],[3,3069],[4,3070]], correct_answer: 1)
Battle.create(question_text: "Which support item would allow you to slow down your enemies so your team can catch them?" ,possible_answers: [[1,3401],[2,3092],[3,3069],[4,3070]], correct_answer: 2)
Battle.create(question_text: "Which support item would speed up your team's movement speed to either catch or escape from an enemy team?" ,possible_answers: [[1,3401],[2,3092],[3,3069],[4,3070]], correct_answer: 3)
Battle.create(question_text: "Which item would allow you to shoot extra bolts on your auto attacks as a ranged champion?" ,possible_answers: [[1,3401],[2,3092],[3,3069],[4,3085]], correct_answer: 4)
Battle.create(question_text: "Which item would allow you to slow down enemy units you hit with your spells?" ,possible_answers: [[1,3085],[2,3116],[3,3069],[4,3085]], correct_answer: 2)
Battle.create(question_text: "Which item would allow to turn invulnerable, but unable to act, avoiding damage and allowing abilities to come off cooldown?" ,possible_answers: [[1,3085],[2,3116],[3,3157],[4,3085]], correct_answer: 3)
Battle.create(question_text: "Which item would allow to remove all crowd control effects on your character?" ,possible_answers: [[1,3085],[2,3116],[3,3140],[4,3085]], correct_answer: 3)




3401 face of the mountain
3092 frost queens claim
3069 talisman of ascension
3070 tear of the goddess
3085 runaan's hurricane
3116 rylai's crystal scepter
3157 zhonyas hourglass
3140 quicksilver sash